karvy.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy | Karvy Corporate

The privacy policy of KARVY  assures users of our website that all personal information furnished to us via the website is maintained with the utmost confidentiality and is unshared under most circumstances( unless specially solicited by us and permitted by you). We respect your privacy and wish you a hassle free experience with our website.

**Website Navigation  
**  
Most sections of our website can be viewed without furnishing any of your personal information. Certain sections of the website allow only restricted access and you could be asked for your personal information for identification / authentication purposes and granting access only.

**Registration with Website  
**  
Users can register on the Karvy website by fulfilling the information requirements. The information collected during the registration process (e.g. name, address, e-mail, contact numbers etc.) is used to identify you as a user and sending you requested information from time to time.

Data with regard to the usage of resources on the website also constitute personal information and could be used for analysis of our services and enhance the value of our online offerings with time. We aim to keep you updated with our latest offerings and build a long standing relationship with you.

Subscription to listed electronic communication services results in communications from KARVY as specified in the terms and conditions of the service. The option to unsubscribe is provided along with all online communications.

We do not solicit information in any form if you have indicated that you do not want to do not ant to furnish the same at any point of time.

**Information Protection  
**  
All user information collected by us through the website is maintained confidentially and not shared (transferred, sold or divulged to third parties). The information may occasionally be used by business and channel partners for marketing and advertising requirements in relation to our services.

No information is disclosed to third parties without your consent.

**Use of Cookies  **

The use of cookies by our website is intended to monitor site usage whenever a user accesses our website and its services. Cookies contain information that you provide such as your username and password. We use cookies on our site to help us understand what pages are frequently visited and to improve the web site experience. A cookie cannot affect data on your computer and cannot provide us with information about other sites you have visited.

Your web browser can be set not accept cookies or to warn you before accepting a cookie. If you wish to access secured sections of our web site, you will have to enable per-session cookies in Microsoft Internet Explorer. Most sections in our website can be accessed without accepting a cookie.

**COMMENTS / FEEDBACK**

Do write in to E-mail on any concerns regarding our privacy policy.

## Invest Now with Karvy

Register With Us & Experience Growth

## Partner with Karvy

Partner With Us & Experience Growth
